adventureinyou.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - Adventure In You

**Effective: November 2016**

 **Adventure in You PTE. LTD**. (‘Adventureinyou.com’, ‘AIY’ ‘we’, ‘us’, ‘company”, ‘website’ and/or ‘our’) is committed to protecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a ‘User’) of the website (‘Site’, ‘Service’). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the company.

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## CONTACTING US

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller in respect of any personal data that you submit to us is Adventure In You PTE. LTD, a company incorporated under Singapore law and whose registered office is at 30 Cecil St, #19-06, Singapore 049712.

If you want to know what information we hold about you or if you have any other queries in relation to this privacy policy, please contact us using the following contact information:

Adventure In You PTE. LTD  
30 Cecil St, #19-06, Singapore 049712

For any further clarifications and questions, you can also directly contact us via email at contact@adventureinyou.com.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We will collect information that you provide to us when you purchase any of our products and/or register to use our services/site (such information shall include, but may not be limited to, your name, age, debit/credit card information, telephone number, postal address and email address).

Any letters, e-mails, blog comments, responses on Social Media platforms such as Facebook, Pinterest, Instagram, Youtube, and Twitter, or questions written directly to us may be used as blog material for our audience unless specifically requested otherwise. (Part of) these letters or emails, questions or any other feedback may be used in newsletters, blog posts, columns or up-and-coming books.

About your usage of the service/site; that you provide to us in e-mails or letters that you send to us.

And about transactions, you carry out through the service, orders you place and the fulfilment of your orders.

It is possible to view the Adventure In you website without providing any personal details. However, without giving consent you shall not continue to view our website.

We may also receive some information that you submit to any third party website or application that you access through the Service. Both Adventure In You and the owner or operator of that third party website will be the data controller in respect of any such information and you should check the privacy policy of that website to find out how they will use your personal information.

We will only use any information that we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## COOKIES & 3rd PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

 **For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at contact @ adventureinyou.com and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

We authorize analytics partners (such as Google Analytics) to help analyze usage and traffic for our Services. As an example, we may use analytics partners to analyze and measure, in the aggregate, the number of unique visitors to our Services.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website or the companion app or track conversions from Google Adwords ads.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

In addition, advertisers whose advertisements appear on the Service may use and place cookies on your computer and we have no control over this. Please consult the terms and conditions and privacy policy of such third party advertisers to find out how they collect and use your personal data and to establish whether they use cookies and what they may use them for.

## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?

We may use your information in the following ways:

  * to ensure that our Service is delivered in the most effective manner for you and your computer;
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
  * to provide customer service to you in relation to your use of the Service, to deal with enquiries and complaints relating to the use of the Service and to notify you about any changes to our service;
  * to administer, support, improve, optimise and develop our Service;
  * to produce reports which may be used, sold or published by us at our sole discretion provided that any data or reports will be anonymised and not refer to any individual user of the Services;
  * for internal marketing and demographic studies to improve the products and services that we provide; and for security purposes.

We may also use your information to provide you with our email notifications, newsletters and other marketing communications that either you request from us or which you consent to by opting in when completing a registration form on the Service.

You may opt out from receiving such marketing communications from us at any time by notifying us in writing, contacting us at contact@adventureinyou.com or, alternatively, by following the procedure to ‘unsubscribe’ that is specified in the email that you receive.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Other than as expressly set out in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required or permitted by law, we will not share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

You should note that information posted on the public elements of the Service may be visible by users of the Service throughout the world. You should therefore be careful when submitting information about yourself to the Service.

We may disclose your personal information: (i) to any third party to whom disclosure is necessary to enable us to fulfil your orders and provide you with any service to which you have subscribed via the Service; (ii) where required to do so by law or court order; and (iii) to any person to whom disclosure is necessary to enable us to enforce our rights under this Privacy Policy or under our Terms and Conditions.

We may disclose your personal information to Facebook Inc in order to fulfill the Services. You can review Facebook’s Terms of Service [here](https://www.facebook.com/ads/manage/customaudiences/tos.php).

## THIRD PARTY SITES

The Service may contain links to websites or access to applications that are operated by third parties. We do not control and accept no liability or responsibility for those websites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. Please consult the terms and conditions and privacy policy of those third party websites to find out how they collect and use your personal data and to establish whether they use cookies and what they may use them for.

Advertisements contained on our Service operate as links to the advertiser’s website and as such any information they collect by virtue of your clicking on that link will be collected and used by the relevant advertiser in accordance with the privacy policy of that advertiser.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

In common with a number of other websites, the data that we collect from you may be transferred to a cloud service provider which has data servers which are based outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer and the storing and/or processing of your personal data on these servers. We will take all these steps in the Privacy Policy.

Appropriate security measures will be adopted to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. However, you acknowledge that data transmission over the internet is inherently unsecure and that we cannot guarantee the security of data you send over the internet.

Your information will only be held for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires or permits.

## ACCESSING YOUR INFORMATION

You may at any time request access to and/or, if incorrect, rectification of your personal data by contacting us at the address set out in this Privacy Policy or by e-mailing contact@adventureinyou.com.

We reserve the right to ask you for proof of your identity and to charge you a fee of twenty US dollars ($20) to meet our costs in granting any data access request you make.

## ADVERTISERS & SPONSORS DISCLOSURE

Adventureinyou.com is open to forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, and other forms of compensation and/or projects. Despite this, Adventure In You will never recommend and write about products or brands that we don’t personally use or believe in. We will always disclose whether we are receiving any commissions or products for free, or if a trip was sponsored or not.

We are not responsible for the actions of our advertisers or sponsors. If you purchase a product or service based upon a link from my website, you must take action with that company to resolve any issues and NOT with our website. Any product, claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

Certain links on the website are affiliate or referral links. At no additional cost to you, we will earn a small percentage of the sale if you make a purchase through our affiliate link.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Company has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.

We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.

If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site.

Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Last Updated: December 4th 2018**
